5 Tales of Terror From the Biggest Names in Horror
Trapped Ashes is a horror film directed by Sean S. Cunningham.
Trapped in a house of horror, seven people discover that the only way
they'll get out alive is to tell their scariest stories.
Andy (segment "Wraparound"), played by Jayce Bartok.
Tour Guide (segment "Wraparound"), played by Henry Gibson.
Julia (segment "Wraparound"), played by Lara Harris.
Henry (segment "Wraparound"), played by Scott Lowell.
Max (segment "Wraparound"), played by Dick Miller.
Nathalie / Martine (segments "Wraparound"/ "My Twin, The
Worm"), played by Michèle-Barbara Pelletier.
Trapped Ashes is a 2006 American anthology horror
film with segments directed by Sean S.
Cunningham, Joe Dante, Monte Hellman, Ken Russell, and John Gaeta,
and stars Jayce Bartok, Henry Gibson, and Lara Harris.
The film explores themes of vampire, anthology, horror anthology.
The tone is dark.